homechef.com 2019-02-26

# Privacy Policy | Home Chef

Last updated: September 22, 2017

This Privacy Policy is an agreement between you and Relish Labs, LLC. Along with our representatives, officers, shareholders, subsidiaries, affiliates, parents, employees, and agents (collectively “Home Chef” or “we” or “us” or “our”), we provide the Website at [www.homechef.com](https://www.homechef.com/) to you subject to the following Policy, which you acknowledge, agree to and consent to by using the Website.

This Privacy Policy may be amended by us from time to time at our sole discretion. Please periodically review the controlling version of the Policy. By continuing to use the Website subsequent to us making available an amended version of the Policy, you thereby acknowledge, agree and consent to such amendment. You cannot create an account, buy our products or subscribe to our services without agreeing to this policy.

You represent that you are at least 18 years old and not a person barred from receiving services under the laws of the United States or other applicable jurisdictions.

## Information We Collect

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us. “Personally identifiable information” includes individually identifiable information about an individual consumer collected online by us from the individual. The types of personally identifiable information that we may request include the following: (a) your real name, (b) your address information, including postal and e-mail, (c) your telephone number, (d) information regarding any food allergies you may have, (e) your credit card information (such information is not stored with Home Chef but is instead passed through to our payment processor), (f) your internet or mobile activity information, (g) information regarding the products and services you have purchased from us, including your histories and tendencies, and (h) any content, including text, photographs, or other material provided by you.

The purpose of storing this information is to provide you with a personalized experience, to deliver products to you efficiently and to improve the design and performance of the Website. We may store your personally identifiable information alongside non-personally identifiable information as well.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not submit personally identifiable information to us or use the Website.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your Internet activities through your IP address, computer settings or most-recently visited URL. We may also ask you to directly provide certain non-personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your food preferences.

When you use the Website we might insert some instructions on your computer or mobile device. These instructions will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of instruction stored on your hard drive or device, not on our Website. Cookies may help you navigate the Website as easily as possible.

One form of cookie we may use is associated with Google Analytics advertising. Our participation in the Google Analytics program will enable Google to collect non-personally identifying information about your usage of the Website and the Internet. For more about how Google uses that data, and how to opt out of Google Analytics, please see this webpage: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

We may also use web beacons. A web beacon is an invisible graphic on a web page or email that is programmed to collect non-personally identifiable information about the use of a given website or newsletter, such as whether or not an email is opened and viewed.

## Your Illinois and California Privacy Rights

Certain state laws permit our customers who are Illinois or California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties. In particular, the law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of personal information that have been shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To make such a request, please write to us at: to [legal@homechef.com](mailto:legal@homechef.com) or by mail at Home Chef, 400 N. Michigan Ave., Suite 1400, Chicago, IL, 60611; Attention: Legal.  Please allow 30 days for a response.

## “Do Not Track”

Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser “do not track” signals.

## Behavioral Advertising

There are methods to opt out of some behavioral advertising. To learn more about behavioral advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website ([http://www.networkadvertising.org/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)) and the Digital Advertising Alliance website (<http://www.aboutads.info/>).

## How We Use Your Information

We typically use your information to deliver products to you and to improve the design and performance of the Website. We may use your information to deliver to you, among other things, communications, newsletters and marketing materials from us. These messages could include changes to features of our service and additional email messages about our products, services, contests, and promotions that we feel may be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive these types of promotional communications from us, you may select the unsubscribe link which is present in each email, you may contact customer service at any time or you may email [support@homechef.com](mailto:support@homechef.com). Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding special offers, improvements, or other updates from Home Chef. Your information may also be used to personally contact you when necessary.

By using the service, you do consent to us providing your information to third parties that assist us in the operation and delivery of our Website, products and services, or who may communicate with you about offers and services from Home Chef. We will take reasonable steps to require any such third parties to comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not provide access to your personally identifiable information to third parties for any purpose. You may provide us with an email address for a recipient if you wish for us to send them a promotional offer to try our services. We may share your information with such recipients. Such recipients will not be opted in to any third-party marketing distribution lists without their permission.

We may share your information with other companies (including select data cooperatives) whose products and services you may find useful. These companies may contact you in order to provide you with information about these products and services.  If you prefer that we do not share your name and address as provided in this paragraph, please email us at [donotshare@homechef.com](mailto:donotshare@homechef.com). It is important to understand that with some companies, your information must be shared in order to receive services you have requested through the Website.  Opting out of sharing your information for marketing purposes will not prevent your relevant information from being provided to shippers when you order products for delivery or from other sharing for non-marketing purposes. Similarly, this will not prevent us from sharing information as and to the extent it is combined or aggregated (in a non-personally identified manner) or otherwise analyzed by us or our service providers.

Your information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy even if we undergo a business transition. However, we may transfer your information to a successor person or entity upon an acquisition or other corporate reorganization. You hereby consent to such transfers, and we may assign and transfer all of the rights, benefits, duties, and obligations of this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your information if, among other things, we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or if acting with a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with legal process; (2) enforce this Policy or the Terms and Conditions; (3) respond to legal claims; (4) respond to your requests for customer services or transaction completion; or (5) protect the rights, property or personal safety of the Website's users or the public.

If you do not want us to share or disclose your information as stated herein, please do not use the Website or submit personally identifiable information.

## Security and Storage

We primarily store your information in the United States. Some information may be stored elsewhere. You authorize us to do so.

We take commercially reasonable steps to safeguard and deter unauthorized access to your information. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit or debit card number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. Although we take reasonable measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of your information, no e-commerce platform, website, electronic database or system is completely secure.

## Third Party Websites

The Website might contain links to other websites, such as “social media” sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such services. When you submit information or data to third parties, their privacy policies, not ours, will govern their use of the information and data. You should review the privacy policies and terms of service of all such third parties. We do not make any representations regarding the policies or practices of such third parties.

## Accessing or Updating Your Information

We allow you to access and change or modify your information as previously provided. You may do so by contacting us at [support@homechef.com](mailto:support@homechef.com). To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes or modifications. Unfortunately, we cannot always ensure that such changes or modifications will be reflected in all iterations of your information as previously stored.

Please remember that any information that you disclose on public portions of the Website, such as “comments” forums, may become widespread. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personally identifiable information.
